MARCEL OLSEN

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+48 532505258

marcelolsen26@gmail.com

github.com/MarcelOlsen

Wrocław

SKILLS

HTML5 / CSS3

JavaScript / TypeScript

React.js

TailwindCSS / StyledComponents

Next.js / vite / hono

Git / Github / Gitlab

Docker

Python / GoLang / Swift

Google Cloud Platform

Agile / SCRUM

EDUCATION

Computer Science (eng.)

Polish-Japanese Institute of Computer Science

2024 - Currently

ABOUT ME

Hi! I'm Marcel and since I remember I've always been interested in everything computer science. I find web development to be especially fulfilling and fascinating. I have experience in both front-end and back-end development but I consider the former to be my strong suite. Whenever I'm not coding I like to to indoor climb, play guitar and make coffee

EXPERIENCE

Programming Teacher

mlodziprogramisci

September 2024 - currently

- Taught diverse groups of students with varying knowledge and experience levels.
- Guided students through projects ranging from simple apps in MIT's App Inventor to game development in Unity and introductory full-stack web development with various technologies.
- Conducted both on-site and remote classes, requiring the development of engaging and impactful project-based learning activities.
- Adapted teaching strategies to accommodate a variety of skill levels, enhancing personal mastery of both fundamental and advanced concepts to effectively convey knowledge.

Front-end developer

Mapa Wiedzy 2.0

September 2022 - November 2023

- Development and maintenance of a React.js web application and a landing page
- Working on improving UX/UI using Figma
- · Writing clean and maintainable code
- Creating, assigning, and completing tickets in ClickUp
- Debugging, testing, and conducting code reviews for both my own as well as other developers' code
- · Utilizing GitHub as a version control system
- Implementing Redux Kit, Styled Components in conjunction with Ant Design and Axios
- Assisting with deploying the application and landing page